# Aldy Fikhri Muhammad

Sumedang, West Java 45353 | +62 859 - 5158 - 6501 | <u>aldyfikhrimuhammad@gmail.com</u> | https://www.linkedin.com/in/aldyfikhrimuhammad/

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am a Front End Website Developer completely oriented towards high level of detail and pleasant user experience. Supported by a relevant educational background in the field of Information and Technology and with a career path set for the future as a web developer, and with skills in using supporting technologies such as Javascript, VueJS, Bootstrap, Restful API using Axios Also critical thinking skills, teamwork and good problem solving, will be very useful and easy to implement in the developed program.

#### **EXPERIENCES**

FOCCU INDONESIA (August 2021 – Present)

Co - Founder & Front End Web Developer

- Established an agency engaged in web development and graphic design by inviting several partners to create a complete and stable position structure.
- Establish rules and regulate the running of the business from various aspects in order to create a positive and growing work culture within the agency that is built.
- Making and developing websites with the team with the aim of making it easier for prospective clients to find out details and contact us easily.

#### **BELUM USAI THRIFTSHOP**

(May 2020 - Present)

**Business** owner

- Established a business that is engaged in clothing needs that focus on pre-owned products with the aim of helping MSME entrepreneurs expand their market reach.
- Set the right marketing strategy in order to create a stable forum/community to be able to market products with repeated orders.
- Recording the flow of money in detail so that a transparent and easy system is formed to read the development of the business being built.

### **BARKOPI ANGKRINGAN**

(September 2020 - February 2021)

**Business Owner** 

- Establish a business engaged in the culinary field that can be reached by all people with the aim of creating an unlimited market.
- Continue to innovate by creating and developing new menus so that customers remain in the market that has been formed.
- Maintain good relations between suppliers business owners and customers so as to create a stable and good economic cycle.

#### PT. PERMODALAN NASIONAL MADANI

(May 2019 - August 2019)

Sales Representative

- Conduct sales of products sold by the company continuously in order to achieve the set sales targets.
- Establishing relationships between companies and buyers consisting of customer groups of PT.

  Permodalan Nasional Madani in order to create a system that provides mutual benefits to each other.
- Perform assistance tasks at the branch of PT. Permodalan Nasional Madani is the parent company so that sales employees can be well received by other employees.

PT. KORDON PUTRA (May 2018 – June 2018)

IT Staff (Internship)

• Installing CCTV devices in sub-business units owned by the company in order to create a safe and well supervised environment.

- Maintain and ensure that technology-based company inventory runs well and does not experience functional defects when used by its users.
- Repair company-owned technology-based equipment as quickly as possible when it malfunctions.

RSUD SUMEDANG (October 2016 – January 2017)

IT Staff (Internship)

- Installing a comprehensive computer network in the new building belonging to the Sumedang Hospital with a high level of tidiness and detail so that maintenance can be carried out easily in the future.
- Ensure that technology-based company inventory runs well and does not experience functional defects that will interfere with its users.
- Perform repairs on assets belonging to the Sumedang Hospital based on technology equipment so that
  they can be reused as soon as possible by users and do not interfere with the course of activities.

## **EDUCATION**

**SMK NEGERI 1 SUMEDANG** 

(May 2015 – May 2018)

(March 2022 - April 2022)

Grade: 88/100

# Non-Formal Education & Certification

**Chandradimuka Jabar Coding Camp** 

Computer and Network Engineering

Vue.js Web Frontend Development Grade: 94/100 (Mastered)

Linkedin Learning (December 2021)

Become a Front-End Web Developer Certificate of Completion

PT. Skyline Semesta (March 2018)

Certificate of Competency Grade: 88/100

RSUD Sumedang (October 2016 – January 2017)

Field Work Practice - SIMRS Staff Grade: 94/100

#### **SKILLS**

**Hard Skills Soft Skills** HTML **Critical Thinking** CSS Logical Thinking Javascript **Problem Solving Bootstrap** Team Leadership VueJS Team Work Axios Innovation Git Creativity Web Development Networking Web Design Communication Computer Network **Analytical Skills**